Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Political Science, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Department of Political Science, records
1919-1988
SC0124
Stanford University. Department of Political Science.
11 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfers, 1974-1992.
Information about Access
The materials are partially restricted The faculty personnel files and the student grade files (Boxes 1-7 and 10) are closed to researchers. The student correspondence files, the departmental records, and the miscellaneous faculty papers (Boxes 8 and 9) are open to researchers.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Records include personnel files of faculty, 1923-1988; grade files and letters of recommendation on a sampling of students, 1919-1955; correspondence files of the same students, 1924-1957; miscellaneous departmental minutes, statistics, and memoranda, 1946-73; and miscellaneous correspondence, articles, clippings, and other papers of several faculty members. Of note in the miscellaneous faculty papers is correspondence between Edwin A. Cottrell and Charles Fairman during World War II while Fairman was on duty with the Armed Services; text of a debate between Willmoore Kendall and Mulford Sibley, 1959, on "War and the Use of Force;" and lectures of Chester H. Rowell, 1933, for the course on current international politics.
The student correspondence files, largely with Edwin A. Cottrell, pertain to their experiences in graduate school, in the Armed Services, and in their jobs. Of note are files for Merrill J. Collett pertaining to his work in public administration, 1935-45; J. Lyle Cunningham on his work with the County of Los Angeles and the U.S. Dept. of the Interior, 1933-46; Robert R. Gros pertaining to Democratic politics, 1940s; and Adolph H. Levy pertaining to city management, 1934-42.
Access Terms
Collett, Merrill J.; Cottrell, Edwin Angell, 1881-; Cunningham, J. Lyle.; Fairman, Charles.; Gros, Robert R.; Kendall, Willmoore, 1909-1967.; Levy, Adolph H.; Rowell, Chester Harvey, 1867-1948.; Sibley, Mulford Quickert.; Stanford University. Department of Political Science.; Political science--Study and teaching; Public administration.; World War, 1939-1945
Collection Contents
- Records
  - FACULTY FILES RESTRICTED
    Restricted. Files are closed.
    - Anderson, William (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Angus, Henry F. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Barclay, Thomas S. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Barnett, Vincent M. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Belknap, George M. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Berman, Harold (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Best, Gary L. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Blackman, O.H. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bone, Hugh A. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Borys, Jurij (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Bunzel, John H. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Campbell, Warren M. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Clokie, Hugh McD. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Cole, Kenneth C. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Connery, Robert H. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Corwin, Edwin S. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Cotter, Cornelius P. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Cottrell, Edwin A. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Crane, Robert T. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Crawford, Finla Goff (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Cresap, Dean R. (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Derthick, Marth Ann (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Duggar, George S. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Eagleton, Clyde (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Edy, John N. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Enarson, Harold L. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Fairman, Charles (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Fearing, Flora May (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Finer, Herman (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Finlay, David J. (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Gable, Richard (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Gottfried, Alex (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Grambs, Harold (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - de Grazia, Alfred (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Harlow, Rex (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Harris, Joseph P. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Hazard, John N. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Holsti, Rudolf (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Hsueh, Chun-tu (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Hyneman, Charles S. (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Jenkins, Edward C. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Johnston, Robert L. (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Jordan, Gerald I. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Kawai, Kazuo (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Kendall, Willmoore (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Kerr, George H. (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Kerwin, Jerome G. (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Lane, Robert E. (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Leavelle, Arnaud B. (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Lerner, Ralph M. (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Lippincott, Benjamin E. (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Lipson, Leslie M. (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Lory, Hillis (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Lowenstein, Allard K. (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - McClelland, Charles A. (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - McCoy, Charles N.R. (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - MacMahon, Arthur W. (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Malik, Charles (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Mander, Linden A. (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - Mansfield, Harvey C. (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Martin, Boyd A. (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Masland, John W. (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Mason, Alpeus T. (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Mason, John Brown (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Maynard, David M. (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Middlebush, Frederick A. (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Morgan, Glenn G. (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Murray, Paul R. (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Odegard, Peter H. (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Oppenheim, Felix E. (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Pollock, James K. (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Quigley, Harold S. (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Ralston, jackson H. (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Rankin, Robert S. (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Redlich, Joseph (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Rowell, Chester H. (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Rupley, Joseph W. (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Salter, John L. (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Sansom, Sir George B. (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Saunders, Allen F. (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Sayegh, Fayez (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Sayre, Wallace S. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Scelle, George (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Schuck, Victoria (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Schuman, Frederick L. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Sibley, Mulford Q. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Slusser, Robert M. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Smith, David G. (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Smith, J. Malcolm (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Soltan, Roger H. (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Spalding, Merrill P. (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Spellacy, Edmund F. (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Spencer, Henry R. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Spiro, Herbert J. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Sprout, Harold H. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Stover, Carl F. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Stowell, Ellery C. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Stuart, Graham (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Thompson, Walter (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Travis, Martin B., Jr. (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Tucker, Robert W. (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Ukai, Nobuschige (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Waldo, Dwight (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Wallace, Schuyler C. (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Wasserman, Louis (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Weiss, Herbert F. (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - White, Leonard D. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Wilson, Robert R. (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Windrich, Elaine (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Wright, Benjamin (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Yu, George T. (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Zawodny, Janusz K. (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1989-079
  - PERSONNEL FILES
    - Abramowitz, Alan (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Amstutz, J. Bruce (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, John (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bachman, David (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Barnum, David (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Bay, Christian (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Bender, Gerald (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Benedict, Kennette (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Berman, Marshall (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Bernstein, Karen (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Bianco, William (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Blacker, Coit D. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Blecker, Robert (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Blumenthal, Irene (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Boesche, Roger (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Bonilla, Frank/Ford Foundation Agreement (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Bonilla, Frank (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Bonilla, Frank (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Boschi, Renato (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Botz, Gerhard (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Brecher, Michael (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Breiner, Peter (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Brenner, Michael (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Brown, Donald P. (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Buck-Morss, Susan (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Brunner, Yale (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Buck, Philip (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Burns, James MacGregor (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Cahill, Fred V. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Cahn, Linda (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Cakmek, Cem (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Caldwell, Dan (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Casper, Jonathan D. (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Cary, Charles (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Cater, S. Douglass, Jr. (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Chamberlain, Heath B. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Cocks, Paul (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Chaui, Marilena de Souza (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Cheresky, Isidoro (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Chubb, John: Tenure (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Chubb, John (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Collie, Melissa P. (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Cohen, Bernard (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Cohen, Michael D. (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Col, Jeanne Marie (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Corning, Peter A. (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Dahrendorf, Ralf (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Danzinger, James M. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Davis, Angela (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - dos Santos, Wanderley Guilherme (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - DiPalma, Guiseppe (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Doolin, Dennis James (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Drachkovitch, Milorad M. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Durham, Kathy (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Eisenstein, James (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Ekman, Paul (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Elazar, Daniel J. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Ellsberg, Daniel (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Emmerson, John K. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Encarnation, Dennis (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Eyestone, Robert (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Farley, Phil (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Finer, Samuel (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Fingar, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Finley, David D. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Fiorina, Morris P. (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Flanagan, Scott C. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Flax, Jane (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Florig, Dennis (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Friedland, Edward (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Friedrich, Robert (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Fry, Brian R. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Game, Christopher (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Genco, Stephen J. (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Gerlich, Peter (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Goggin, Malcolm L. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Goldenberg, Edie N. (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Goldman, Ralph (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Gould, William (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Greenberg, Edward S. (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Griffiths, Franklyn (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Gromadzki, Grzegorz (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Grossman, Naava Binder (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Habib, Philip C. (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Hadari, Saguiv (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Haftendorn, Helga (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Hagen, Michael G. (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Hanley, Paul (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Harris, Christina Phelps (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Hartsock, Nancy (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Harsanyi, John (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Haselkorn, Avigdor (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Hawley, James (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Hellman, Donald C. (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Hennessy, Bernard (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Henningsen, Manfred (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Holsti, Ole (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Hull, Hadlai (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Hutter, Horst (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Harding, Harry (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Jacobsen, Gary (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Jaguaribe, Helio (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Jenkins, George (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Jensen, Donald N. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Jonsson, Christer (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Juster, Richard (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Kato, Tetsuro (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Kaplan, John (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Kaufman, Edy/Nazzal, Nafez (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Kavanagh, Dennis (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Keohane, Robert O. (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Knight, Mary Ann (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Knothe, Tomasz (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Kothari, Rajni (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Kronick, Bernard L. (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Kuklinski, James (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Levy, Jack (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Larson, Deborah (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Larson, Jolene (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Ladd, Everett (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Lagerstrom, Richard P. (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Lijphart, Arend (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Laing, James Dwight (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - LaPorte, Todd R. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Leiserson, Michael (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Levin, Martin (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Li, Victor (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Lowenkopf, Martin (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Luebbert, Gregory lM. (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Lyman, Peter (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Markovitz, Inga (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Margolis, Larry (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Marks, Gary (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Martinelli, Alberto (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Mayntz, Renate (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Mazrui, Ali A. (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Meyers, Gary (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Mollenkopf, John (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Mols, Manfred (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Mozingo, David P. (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Murray, Douglas P. (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - McCubbins, Mathew D. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - McCloskey, Paul N. Jr. (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - McCloskey, Paul N. Jr. (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - McAlister, John (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - McCloskey, Robert G. (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - McKinnon, Catherine (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - McNeil, Francis J. (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Nau, Henry R. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Nakagawa, Go (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Nie, Norman H. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Noel, Robert (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Nnoli, Okwudiba (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Oksenberg, Michel C. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Olsen, Johan P. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Orrego Vicuna, Francisco (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Orfield, Gary (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Paff, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Page, Benjamen (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Pateman, Carole (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Peabody, Robert (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Pedersen, Mogens (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Peterson, Paul (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pirages, Dennis (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Poduzov, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Polsby, Nelson (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Pool, Jonathan (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Potter, William C. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Powell, G. Bingham (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Pritchett, C. Herman (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Prewitt, Kenneth (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Platt, Alan (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Pravda, Alex (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Quick, Stephen Adee (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Quinley, Hal (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Ra Jong-Yil (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Rittberger, Volker (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Rogat, Yosal (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Rogow, Arnold (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Rokkan, Stein (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Rose, Lawrence (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Rose-Ackerman, Susan (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Roseman, Cyril (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Rosencranz, Armin (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Rosenzweig, Robert M. (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Rue, John E. (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Sabel, Charles F. (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Sabel, Charles F. (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Sanderson, Steven E. (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Sartori, Giovanni (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Saxonhouse, Arlene W. (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Schabert, Tilo (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Schmidt, Manfred G. (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Scheinberg, Seymour (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Shafer, Byron E. (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Shapiro, Martin (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Share, Donald (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Shell, Kurt L. (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Shillinglaw, Geoffrey M. (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Skocpol, Theda (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Smith, William (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Smoke, Richard L. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Sokol, Anthony E. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Smith, Kent (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Starr, John (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Stenelo, Lars-Goren (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Stock, Walter (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Strom, Kaare (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Stuart, Graham (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Suian, Pavel G. (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Sullivan, Denis (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Tarrow, Sidney (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Taylor, J. Serge (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Tanter, Raymond (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Thai, Nguyen Huu (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Thompson, Dennis (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Tilly, Charles (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Tsebelis, George (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Verba, Sidney (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Von Beyme, Klaus (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Voegelin, Eric H. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Walker, Robert A. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Watkins, James T. (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Wallensteen, Peter (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Walzer, Michael L. (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Weiler, Lawrence D. (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Weiler, Lawrence D. (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Weinstein, Franklin (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Williams, Raymond H. (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Weiss, Carter (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - White, James (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Whiting, Van R. Jr. (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Whiting, Alan (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Wildavsky, Aaron (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Willard, Matthew (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Weatherford, Stephen (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Winckler, Edwin (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Wolfe, Alan (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Wolfinger, Raymond (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Woolpert, Stephen B. (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Yoffie, David (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Young, Richard P. (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Yu, Kuan Tsyh Steven (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Zatz, Julie (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Zeigler, Harmon (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Zimmermann, Ekkart (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Zisk, Betty Hershberger (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Teacher Evaluations by Students
    - Anderson, John B., 1980-81 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Bachman, David, 1984-85 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Bernstein, Karen, 1986-87 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Bianco, William, 1985-86 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Blacker, Coit, 1987-88 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Blecker, Robert A., 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Boshi, Renato, 1985-86 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Brecher, Michael, 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Collie, Melissa P., 1984-85 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Chubb, John, 1978-83 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Flax, Jane, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Florig, Dennis, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Genco, Stephen J., 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Goggin, Malcolm, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Haftendorn, Helga, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Harding, Harry, 1973-83 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Teacher Evaluations by Students
    - Hutter, Horst, 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Keohane, Nannerl, 1973-81 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Keohane, Robert, 1975-81 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Larson, Jolene, 1975-78 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Levy, Jack, 1985-87 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Lewis, John W., 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Marks, Gary, 1979-82 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Martinelli, Albert, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Mayntz, Renate, 1983-84 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - McCloskey, Paul, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Meyers, Gary, 1980-81 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Nau, Henry, 1976-77 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Pavada, Alex, 1985-86 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Rittberger, Volker, 1985-86 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Saxonhouse, Arlene, 1984-85 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Share, Donald, 1982-83 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Tsebelis, George, 1985-86 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Weinstein, Franklin, 1980-81 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Whiting, Van, 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Yoffee, David, 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Zatz, Julie, 1981-82 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - DEPARTMENT RECORDS (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous department records, 1947-59 (minutes, statistics, memoranda) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Memo to prospective women graduate students from current students, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 1A)
  - FACULTY FILES (Box 8)
    - Bunzel, John H., articles, 1960-70 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Cotter, Cornelius P., 1959-60, correspondence, clippings, press releases, book ads (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Cottrell, Edwin A., 1953, clippings, family history, memorial resolution (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Fairman, Charles, 1942-55, correspondence with Cottrell during World War II, clippings (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Kendall, Willmoore, 1957-64, clippings, text of debate with Mulford Sibley on "War and the Use of Force" (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Rowell, Chester H., April-June 1933, lectures from P.S. 123 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Sibley, Mulford, 1959-64, clippings, text of debate with Willmoore Kendall on "War and the Use of Force" (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Stuart, Graham, 1960-65, clippings, biographical sketch, and information on Graham H. Stuart Fund (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - STUDENT FILES
    - Bendetson, Karl R., a.b. June 1929 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Black, Charles A., a.b. January 1941 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Collett, Merrill J., a.b. June 1934 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Colvin, H. Milton (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Cotter, Cornelius P., a.b. April 1949 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Cunningham, J.L., a.b. January 1931 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Estrem, William G., [research paper] (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Fletcher, Charles G., a.b. June 1924 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Fordyce, Jack K., a.b. June 1939 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Foster, Homer (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Gange, John Frederic, a.b. June 1932, M.A. June 1934, 1932, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Gill, John H., a.b. June 1936 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Gray, Barbara K., a.b. April 1945 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Groff, Katherine, a.b. June 1939 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Gros, Robert R., a.b. June 1935 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Hawkins, Robert Z., a.b. June 1925 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Heard, Townsend, a.b. October 1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Holloway, Gilbert N., a.b. June 1936 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, Martin Lee, a.b. June 1953 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Johnson, John R., a.b. September 1946 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Mrs. Samuel G. [donor] (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Kilpatrick, Wylie, a.b. October 1922 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Krueger, De Witte W., a.b. June 1930 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Levy, Adolph H., a.b. June 1928 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Margulies, Fritz A., a.b. June 1950 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - McDowell, Carl E., a.b. April 1932 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Mellinkoff, Abe I., a.b. June 1932 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Merrill, Dorothea, a.b. June 1936 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Millington, Robert, a.b. September 1946 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Moses, Lincoln E. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Mueller, Donald Eugene, a.b. June 1952 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Muller, Willard C., a.b. June 1941 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Munro, William B., a.b. January 1937 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Parker, George A., a.b. June 1938 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Rich, Robert Horton, a.b. June 1941 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Rowland, Gilford G., a.b. June 1923 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Rowland, Mary [department secretary] (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Sawyer, Norman D., a.b. April 1932 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Silberman, David B., a.b. June 1941 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Smith, Barbara Jean, a.b. April 1942 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Stribling, Rebecca, a.b. 1937, M.A. 1938, 1937, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Sullivan, Lola, a.b. June 1953 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Sussman, Peggy, a.b. June 1942 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Sweet, Barbara, a.b. June 1937 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Swim, H. Dudley, a.b. June 1926 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Swope, John R., a.b. June 1955 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Taylor, Marshall K., a.b. June 1930 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Tenny, Stanley W., a.b. June 1931 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Trego, Charlotte, a.b. June 1953 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Tsou, Pang L., a.b. June 1931 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Ushiro, Arthur K., a.b. January 1938 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Varanini, Tina, a.b. June 1943 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Vasey, Thomas K., a.b. April 1932 (Box 9, Folder 39)